a whole new day I can't believe I came
up with 44 ideas yesterday that is
astounding I can't even
that's like infinite possibility I know
it's not infinite it's 44 but considered
I thought 100 was going to be a stretch
and it was going to be a stretch for
that to take two weeks I came up with 44
ideas in a day
I just like to celebrate that success
maybe that's what number 45 is is a
success elevator I think that's kind of
what Facebook already is do too much for
degree because people don't get the full
picture but in a more organized way you
can see them I don't know so we need to
flush that one a little more but a
congratulations app is ID number 45 they
can't all be goal people